http://www.allseasonsuniforms.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy All Seasons Uniforms
Javascript seems to be disabled in your browser.You must have JavaScript enabled in your browser to utilize the functionality of this website.
Work Clothes Home
Brand NamesA+ Career Apparel Ash CityFleeceOuterwearPolosSoft ShellSweatshirtsVestsASW Jackets BackpackerWoven ShirtsPolosOuterwearVestsBagsBaysideBenchmark FR Berne WorkwearBib OverallsCoverallsGlovesHeadwearOuterwearPants / Jeans / ShortsShirtsSweatshirtsVests Big Bill FRBib Overalls / CoverallsHeadwearLabwearOuterwearPants / JeansShirtsSweatshirtsT-Shirts / Henleys Big Bill WorkwearAccessories / HeadwearBase LayersBib Overalls / CoverallsJacketsPantsT-ShirtsWoven ShirtsVestsBig SmithBlue Generation BulwarkBib OverallsCoverallsHeadwearLabwearOuterwearPantsShirts / HenleysWoven Shirts CamberHenleysPantsPolosSweatshirtsT-Shirts CarharttBib Overalls / CoverallsHatsJacketsJeansRainwearShirts / HenleysSweatshirtsVestsWoven Shirts Charles RiverFleecesJacketsPantsShirtsSoft Shell JacketsSweatshirtsVests Chef DesignsApronsButcher CoatsChef CoatsChef PantsChef ShirtsHeadwearVestsDevon & Jones DickiesAccessoriesBib OverallsCoats / Jackets / VestsCoverallsJeansPantsPolosShirts / HenleysShortsSweatshirtsWoven ShirtsDri-Duck Earl's ApparelPainter's ClothesPantsShorts EdwardsShirtsPantsPolosHousekeeping / HospitalityChef ClothesApronsCardigansJacketsOuterwearNeckwearShortsSkirtsSweatersVestsExtra Wide Sock Co.ExtremeGard Fashion Seal HealthcareScrub TopsScrub BottomsWarm-UpsChef ClothesCoverallsDressesGownsHeadwearHousekeepingLabwearPatient ApparelProtective CoatsSkirts Fruit of the LoomT-ShirtsSweatshirts GildanPolosHoodiesT-ShirtsGung Ho Apparel HanesPolosSweatshirtsT-ShirtsHarriton JerzeesPolosSweatshirtsT-Shirts Key IndustriesAccessoriesBib OverallsCoats / Jackets / VestsCoverallsJeans / DungareesShirtsShortsSweatshirtsT-Shirts / HenleysUndergarmentsKing Louie LandauScrub TopsScrub BottomsWarm-UpsLabwearLiberty OccuNomixBib Overalls/CoverallsHoodies/SweatshirtsHeadwear/AccessoriesJacketsPantsT-ShirtsVestsPolosPort & CompanyPort Authority PortwestAccessoriesCleanroomCoveralls / Bib OverallsHeadwearOuterwearPainter's ClothesPantsWoven ShirtsVestsSweatshirtsT-Shirts Red KapAccessoriesCoveralls / Bib OverallsHousekeepingJacketsJeansLab CoatsPantsPolosShortsT-ShirtsWoven ShirtsRound House SmittenScrub TopsScrub Bottoms Snap 'N' WearAccessoriesCoverallsJacketsShirtsSweatshirtsVestsWindbreakers SportsmasterJacketsPants / ShortsShirts Sport-TekT-ShirtsPolosOuterwearSweatshirtsBottomsStan Ray ApparelTecgen Select ToppsBib Overalls / CoverallsCoats / JacketsPantsShirtsLabwearTough Duck Uncommon ThreadsApronsChef CoatsChef HatsChef PantsChef Shirts Union LineAccessoriesBib Overalls / CoverallsJeans / PantsOuterwearShirtsT-Shirts / HenleysSweatshirts Universal OverallFace MasksAccessoriesCoats / JacketsCoverallsLab Coats / Shop CoatsPaintingPants / ShortsShirts UrbaneScrub TopsScrub JacketsScrub BottomsWalls WonderWinkScrub TopsScrub BottomsScrub CapScrub Dresses / Scrub SkirtsWarm-UpsLabwear WorklonBoots / Shoe CoversCoverallsFrocksHoods / HeadwearIntershirts / InterpantsLab CoatsWrangler Wrangler RiggsBib OverallsOuterwearPants/JeansShirtsShorts
American MadeAccessories Bib OverallsInsulated / LinedUnlined CoverallsInsulated / Lined Hoodies / SweatshirtsZipper FrontsPulloversHalf Zips / Quarter Zips OuterwearJacketsWindbreakersWindshirtsVests Pants / ShortsJeans / DungareesPantsShortsSweatpants Shirts / TopsWoven ShirtsPolo / Golf ShirtsT-Shirts / Henleys Undergarments / SocksSocks
Occupation Custom Athletic Team Apparel & ClothesCustom Athletic Team FleecesCustom Athletic Team Sweatshirts & HoodiesCustom Athletic Team JacketsCustom Athletic Team SweatpantsCustom Athletic Team Golf Shirts & PolosCustom Athletic Team Soft Shell JacketsCustom Athletic Team T-ShirtsCustom Athletic Team ShortsCustom Athletic Team VestsCustom Athletic Team Windshirts Mechanic Clothes & Automotive WorkwearCoveralls & JumpsuitsShirtsPants / ShortsJackets / CoatsBelts, Caps, & Gloves Cleanroom / ESDBootsBouffant CapsCoverallsFacemasksFrocksHoodsIntershirtsInterpantsLab Coats / Lab JacketsShoe Covers Flame ResistantAccessoriesBib OverallsCoats / JacketsCoverallsExtrication WearHeadwearHoodsJeans / DungareesLab CoatsLinersPantsParkasShirtsSquad / Flight SuitsSweatshirtsT-Shirts / HenleysUndergarmentsVestsWildland Wear Freezer WearBib OverallsCoverallsHoodsJackets / Parkas / Vests Chef / Food ApparelApronsButcher Coats / FrocksChef Coats / JacketsChef ShirtsChef PantsHeadwear Medical UniformsCounter CoatsLab Coats / Lab JacketsProtective Coats / Gowns High VisibilityAccessoriesBib OverallsCoverallsHeadwearHoodsHoodies / SweatshirtsJackets / CoatsPantsShirts / T-ShirtsVests HospitalityAccessoriesApronsCasino ApparelShirtsSuit Separates HousekeepingDressesPantsSmocksTea ApronsTunics HuntingBib OverallsHeadwearJacketsPants / ShortsShirts / T-ShirtsVests Military / TacticalCoverallsHoodies / SweatshirtsJackets / Coats / ParkasPantsShirtsShorts Nursing ScrubsScrub TopsScrub BottomsWarm-UpsCoverallsHeadwearScrub Dresses / Skirts Painter's ClothingPantsBib OverallsCoverallsApronsCapsJacketsShirtsShorts Public Safety / SecurityAccessoriesBeltsBlazers / CoatsCoverallsHeadwearOuterwearPants / TrousersSafety VestsShirtsShortsSkirtsSweatshirts
Men's AccessoriesApronsBagsBeltsBlanketsHeadwearHoodsNeckwear Bib OverallsUnlinedInsulated / Lined CoverallsInsulated / LinedUnlinedGloves Hoodies / SweatshirtsHalf Zips / Quarter ZipsPulloversZipper Fronts OuterwearFleeceSoft ShellCoats / JacketsLinersParkasVestsWindshirts Pants / JeansPantsCargoDungareesInsulated / LinedJeans RainwearBib OverallsJackets / CoatsPants Shirts / TopsWoven ShirtsPolo / Golf ShirtsT-Shirts / HenleysShorts Suit SeparatesBlazers / CoatsDress PantsVests SweatersCardigansPulloversVests Undergarments / SocksUndergarmentsSocks
Women's AccessoriesBlanketsNeckwear Coveralls / Bib OverallsInsulated / LinedUnlined Dresses / SkirtsDressesSkirts Hoodies / SweatshirtsHalf Zips / Quarter ZipsZipper FrontsPullovers OuterwearFleeceJacketsSoft ShellVests Pants / JeansJeansPants Shirts / TopsPolo / Golf ShirtsT-Shirts / HenleysWoven ShirtsMaternityShorts Suit SeparatesBlazers / CoatsDress PantsDress SkirtsVestsSweaters Undergarments / SocksSocks
Kid's Bib Overalls / CoverallsUnlinedInsulatedHoodies / Sweatshirts OuterwearJacketsPants Shirts / TopsPolo / Golf ShirtsWoven ShirtsT-ShirtsShorts
PPE
Clearance/Deals
Build A Uniform Workshop
Welcome Guest
All Seasons Uniforms, Inc.
Search:
Search
Cart Subtotal
(0)
US$
Recently added item(s)
Cart is Empty
Remove This Item
Edit item
x US$
View Cart
Proceed to Checkout
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Register
Login
Menu
Brand Names
Featured Brands
Red Kap
Bulwark
Dickies
Screen Printing
COVID-19 UPDATEWe now have face masks!
50%OFFYour 1st Embroidered Logo*
Click for Embroidery Quote
Home
/
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which All Seasons Uniforms, Inc. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.allseasonsuniforms.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by All Seasons Uniforms, Inc.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the siteplace an ordersubscribe to the newsletter and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information,
Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously.
We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
All Seasons Uniforms, Inc. collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:
To improve customer service
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
To personalize user experience
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To improve our Site
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
To process transactions
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
To send periodic emails
The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.
Changes to this privacy policy
All Seasons Uniforms, Inc. has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page,. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
All Seasons Uniforms, Inc.
www.allseasonsuniforms.com
1320 Zimmerman Rd. Woodstock, IL 60098
847-952-9860
webmaster@allseasonsuniforms.com
Address
1320 Zimmerman Rd
Woodstock, IL 60098
Call Us Toll Free
(888) 725 7327
Fax (847) 952 0480
Customer Service Hours:
Mon - Fri: 8 AM - 4 PM Central
sales@allseasonsuniforms.com
Subscribe to our mailing list
Social Media
Customer ServiceShipping PolicyReturns/ExchangesCreate an AccountContact UsFrequently Asked Questions (FAQ) ServicesCustom EmbroideryScreen Printing Shop With UsGSA Contract Company InformationAbout UsPrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsSite MapBlog
© 2020 All Seasons Uniforms,Inc. All rights reserved.
To top
